gminsidenews.com 2007-12-10

# GMInsideNews Forums - FAQ: General Board Rules

| Register | FAQ | Members List | Calendar | vBGarage | Mark Forums Read  
---|---|---|---|---|---  

General Terms of Service  
---  
New Page 3

_**General Terms of Service**_

Please remember that we are not responsible for any messages posted. _Federal law, specifically the Communications Decency Act, 47 U.S.C.A §230, states that website publishers are immune from any liability for statements authored by others._ We do not vouch for or warrant the accuracy, completeness or usefulness of any message, and are not responsible for the contents of any message. 

The messages express the views of the author of the message, not necessarily the views of this bulletin board. Any user who feels that a posted message is objectionable is encouraged to contact us immediately by email. We have the ability to remove objectionable messages and we will make every effort to do so, within a reasonable time frame, if we determine that removal is necessary. 

You agree, through your use of this service, that you will not use this bulletin board to post any material which is knowingly false and/or defamatory, inaccurate, abusive, vulgar, hateful, harassing, obscene, profane, sexually oriented, threatening, invasive of a person's privacy, or otherwise violative of any law. 

You agree not to post any copyrighted material unless the copyright is owned by you or by this bulletin board.   

General Website Rules  
---  
New Page 2

_**Posting Guidelines for GMInsidenews’s Forums:**_

GMI’s forums were established to create a fun, friendly community to interact in. In order to foster this friendly interaction and create an environment where everyone feels comfortable posting and hanging out, we have created a set of rules and guidelines which all members are required to follow. These rules are general in nature, as it is impossible to spell out every possible offense that may result in a thread being locked, deleted, or edited. 

_**The rules are as follows:**_

1\. Expletives (such as sh*t, f*ck, c*nt, motherf*cker, etc) are not allowed (These have been *’d out here b/c this is the forum rules page). Please refrain from using such words on this forum. 

2\. Spamming or unpaid business advertisements is not allowed. Threads or PMs determined to be "spam" will be deleted or forwarded to the Administration. This type of posting could possibly result with privileges to our board restricted or denied without notice. Lottery schemes being advertised on this board are considered Spam. 

3\. Flames or derogatory insults will not be tolerated. If you disagree with another member's point of view, do so in a mature and civil manner. If someone posts to discuss their personal problems or seek help from other forum members, please do not respond unless you have something positive or helpful to add. If you find yourself being flamed or insulted by another member, please do not dignify that person with a response. Notify a moderator and let us handle it. 

4\. Threads or replies promoting or expressing racist or sexist views will not be tolerated. 

5\. Porn or other 'risque' content is not allowed. There are plenty of websites for such material. This isn't one of them. 

6\. Avatars and Signatures: the same rules that apply to your posts apply to your signatures and avatars. Please keep this in mind when selecting your avatar and/or signature. 

7\. Free posts, or posting solely for the purpose of boosting your post count will not be tolerated. 

Signature and avatar tests will be allowed in the Testing forum, where posts do not count towards your post count. In other forums, they will be treated as free posts. 

8\. Please post your topics in the most appropriate forum (i.e., tech threads only in tech forums). If you post a thread that would be more appropriate in another forum, a moderator will move it for you. However, please do not make the moderators do this for you. Use your judgment to determine which forum(s) best suits your topic. If you are dealing with a TECHNICAL topic and it could appropriately fit in more than one forum, you may post it in multiple forums. Multiple posting or X-Posting should be held to a maximum of 2 forums. 

9\. Controversial topics, such as retardation, racism, sexism, illicit drugs/narcotic, etc., will NOT be tolerated. 

10\. Threads/replies encouraging other illegal/unethical action (like "Best way to kill neighbor's dog?") will not be tolerated. 

11\. "Trolling", or makings posts with the sole intention of creating problems on the forums is obviously against the forum guidelines. This includes registering an alternate account for the sole purpose of creating problems on the forums. "Troll accounts" will be locked immediately and permanently, and can be locked without notification to the offender. 

12\. Threads/replies against or attacking GMI’s policies will not be allowed. 

13\. Persistent or purposeful bashing of members will result in whatever the Administrators deem necessary as punishment after we’ve talked about it. 

14\. Posting a thread or reply to question or criticize moderator or administrator actions is not appropriate in a public forum. Please utilize the board's Private Message function, or e-mail, if you wish to discuss these issues. As long as you bring up your concerns maturely and civilly to the moderator or administrator in question, we will do our best to address your concerns fairly and promptly. 

15\. Posting of copyrighted information on GMI is strictly forbidden and will be removed. GMI will cooperate with any copyright owner who requests contact/other information about a user who posts their copyrighted information.

16\. The chatroom is not moderated at all times. therefore all users post at their own risk.

17\. The Garage is a service provided for free. There are no guarantees made about availably or features. We reserve the right to remove any pictures at any given time with no prior notice. Please do not use the garage at the sole place for images that are important to you. 

18\. You must be 14 years of age or older to post on GMInsidenews.com's forums. Any user who provides info, or gives reason to believe that they are not in compliance with this rule will have their account and prior posts deleted.

 _ **Here are the "Do's" and "Don'ts" of addressing your concerns to moderators or administrators:**_

"Do" be civil and polite. Bring up your concerns in a mature and respectful manner. If you are contacting us because you violated forum guidelines, be adult enough to admit your mistake. If your account has been locked for some reason, talking politely to us about it in private, via e-mail or private message, can get your account reinstated in many cases. 

"Do not" be derogatory or insulting towards us. You will not get what you want by name calling or bashing us. 

All we ask is that you treat us the way you would want us to treat you. If you treat us with respect, we will do the same for you. 

If you violate forum guidelines, in most cases, you can expect the following action from the moderators/administrators: 

1\. First offense- warning via private message, e-mail, and/or moderator reply in the offending thread 

2\. Second offense- something we think is absolutely hilarious to your account. 

3\. Subsequent offense- longer account locks, possibly permanent, or something that is even more hilarious done to your account. 

Please realize that the nature of the offense will determine the action to be taken. If the violation is extreme enough, or has been repeated enough times in the past, a member can have his/her account locked or possibly deleted without a warning. 

Threads or replies that do not comply with our guidelines may be locked, edited, or deleted, depending on the nature of the offense. We will make every effort to state why such action was taken via private message, e-mail, and/or moderator reply in the offending thread. For this reason, we ask that you check your private messages often. You can find out whether or not you have received any private messages by logging into your user Control Panel. You can set your options so that the board notifies you when you have received a private message, if you so desire. 

The above rules and guidelines are necessary to make GMI’s forums comfortable and enjoyable for everyone. If you feel you can not comply with the rules above, please refrain from using GMI’s forums. 

All information and images posted on this site by it's staff and users is/becomes the property of GMInsidenews and it's owners.  

Privacy Policy  
---  
New Page 3 ** WWW.GMINSIDENEWS.COM  
 **

##  **PRIVACY POLICY**

Welcome to www.gminsidenews.com (the "Site").

We understand that privacy online is important to users of our Site, especially when conducting business.   
This statement governs our privacy policies with respect to those users of the Site ("Visitors") who visit without   
transacting business and Visitors who register to transact business on the Site and make use of the various services offered by www.gminsidenews.com (collectively, "Services") ("Authorized Customers").

**"Personally Identifiable Information"**   
refers to any information that identifies or can be used to identify, contact, or locate the person to whom such information pertains, including, but not limited to, name, address, phone number, fax number, email address, financial profiles, social security number, and credit card information. Personally Identifiable Information does not include information that is collected anonymously (that is, without identification of the individual user)   
or demographic information not connected to an identified individual.

**What Personally Identifiable Information is collected?**  
We may collect basic user profile information from all of our Visitors. We collect the following additional information from our Authorized Customers: the names, addresses, phone numbers and email addresses of Authorized Customers, the nature and size of the business, and the nature and size of the advertising inventory that the Authorized Customer intends to purchase or sell.

**What organizations are collecting the information?**  
In addition to our direct collection of information, our third party service vendors (such as credit card companies, clearinghouses and banks) who may provide such services as credit, insurance, and escrow services may collect this information from our Visitors and Authorized Customers. We do not control how these third parties use such information, but we do ask them to disclose how they use personal information provided to them from Visitors and Authorized Customers. Some of these third parties may be intermediaries that act solely as links in the distribution chain, and do not store, retain, or use the information given to them.

**How does the Site use Personally Identifiable Information?**  
We use Personally Identifiable Information to customize the Site, to make appropriate service offerings, and to fulfill buying and selling requests on the Site. We may email Visitors and Authorized Customers about research or purchase and selling opportunities on the Site or information related to the subject matter of the Site. We may also use Personally Identifiable Information to contact Visitors and Authorized Customers in response to specific inquiries, or to provide requested information. If a user post contains copyrighted or proprietary information, the site will use/provide whatever information (email address, ip addresses) needed to allow the entitie who's rights were violated by the posting to contact the offending user. 

**With whom may the information may be shared?**  
Personally Identifiable Information about Authorized Customers may be shared with other Authorized Customers who wish to evaluate potential transactions with other Authorized Customers. We may share aggregated information about our Visitors, including the demographics of our Visitors and Authorized Customers, with our affiliated agencies and third party vendors. We also offer the opportunity to "opt out" of receiving information or being contacted by us or by any agency acting on our behalf. 

**How is Personally Identifiable Information stored?**  
Personally Identifiable Information collected by www.gminsidenews.com is securely stored and is not accessible to third parties or employees of www.gminsidenews.com except for use as indicated above.

**What choices are available to Visitors regarding collection, use and distribution of the information?**  
Visitors and Authorized Customers may opt out of receiving unsolicited information from or being contacted by us and/or our vendors and affiliated agencies by responding to emails as instructed, or by contacting us at [admin@gminsidenews.com](mailto:admin@gminsidenews.com)

**Are Cookies Used on the Site?**  
Cookies are used for a variety of reasons. We use Cookies to obtain information about the preferences of our Visitors and the services they select. We also use Cookies for security purposes to protect our Authorized Customers. For example, if an Authorized Customer is logged on and the site is unused for more than 10 minutes, we will automatically log the Authorized Customer off.

**How does www.gminsidenews.com use login information?**  
www.gminsidenews.com uses login information, including, but not limited to, IP addresses, ISPs, and browser types, to analyze trends, administer the Site, track a user's movement and use, and gather broad demographic information.

**What partners or service providers have access to Personally Identifiable Information from Visitors and/or Authorized Customers on the Site?**  
www.gminsidenews.com has entered into and will continue to enter into partnerships and other affiliations with a number of vendors.  
Such vendors may have access to certain Personally Identifiable Information on a need to know basis for evaluating Authorized Customers for service eligibility.   
Our privacy policy does not cover their collection or use of this information.   
Disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information to comply with law. We will disclose Personally Identifiable Information in order to comply with a court order or subpoena or a request from a law enforcement agency to release information. We will also disclose Personally Identifiable Information when reasonably necessary to protect the safety of our Visitors and Authorized Customers. 

**How does the Site keep Personally Identifiable Information secure?**  
All of our employees are familiar with our security policy and practices. The Personally Identifiable Information of our Visitors and Authorized Customers is only accessible to a limited number of qualified employees who are given a password in order to gain access to the information. We audit our security systems and processes on a regular basis. Sensitive information, such as credit card numbers or social security numbers, is protected by encryption protocols, in place to protect information sent over the Internet. While we take commercially reasonable measures to maintain a secure site, electronic communications and databases are subject to errors, tampering and break-ins, and we cannot guarantee or warrant that such events will not take place and we will not be liable to Visitors or Authorized Customers for any such occurrences. 

**How old do I have to be to use the site?**

To join GMI's forums, you must be 14 years or older.

**How can Visitors correct any inaccuracies in Personally Identifiable Information?**  
Visitors and Authorized Customers may contact us to update Personally Identifiable Information about them or to correct any inaccuracies by emailing us at [admin@gminsidenews.com](mailto:admin@gminsidenews.com)

**Can a Visitor delete or deactivate Personally Identifiable Information collected by the Site?**  
We provide Visitors and Authorized Customers with a mechanism to delete/deactivate Personally Identifiable Information from the Site's database by contacting [admin@gminsidenews.com](mailto:admin@gminsidenews.com). However, because of backups and records of deletions, it may be impossible to delete a Visitor's entry without retaining some residual information. An individual who requests to have Personally Identifiable Information deactivated will have this information functionally deleted, and we will not sell, transfer, or use Personally Identifiable Information relating to that individual in any way moving forward. 

**What happens if the Privacy Policy Changes?**  
We will let our Visitors and Authorized Customers know about changes to our privacy policy by posting such changes on the Site. However, if we are changing our privacy policy in a manner that might cause disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information that a Visitor or Authorized Customer has previously requested not be disclosed, we will contact such Visitor or Authorized Customer to allow such Visitor or Authorized Customer to prevent such disclosure. 

**Links:**  
This web site contains links to other web sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are moving to another web site. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policies may differ from ours. 

© 2005 **www.gminsidenews.com** ,  All rights reserved.  
Unauthorized duplication or publication of any materials from this Site is expressly prohibited.    

All times are GMT -5. The time now is 06:11 PM.
